Guide to the Gerald Gillespie Papers SC0581
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2015-055
  - Department of German Studies + University, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Agendas + Members through Academic Year, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Stanford German Studies Programs, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Humanities Program, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Mail, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Gillespie Humanisti, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - German Studies Admissions, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Sec III, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Applications, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Department Business, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Graduate Recruitment, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Stanford German Studies Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - CTIC Proposal, Rev., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Comparative Literature Department + Programs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Archivist/Hoover Institution, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - R.A. Prier Trust/Lawson, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Prier Trust - BA #12485, 0 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Prier Trust 1994 Account (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Prier Trust 1995 Account (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Ray Prier: Testament + Estate, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Prier Trust - BA #10991, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - ACLA, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - ACLA '97 Poetry Paper + ACLA '98 Intl vs. Natl, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ACLA Santa Barbara, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ACLA/ICLA Ann Abor, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - ACLA - Eastern Conference, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ACLA Chapel Hill, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ACLA Emory, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ACLA San Francisco December 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ACLA Advisory Board, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ACLA Board San Francisco, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ACLA Brandeis, March 8-11, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ACLA Chapel HIll, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ACLA Berkeley-Stanford bid, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Trahan CL+IS (ACLA), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ACLA, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ACLA, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - ACLA Bloomington, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - ACLA Claremont, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Anhropological Time Warps (ACLA), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - ACLA, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - DGAVL, 2005-2011 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - ICLA Brussels, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - ICLA Workshop "Modernist Terrains", 2002 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - ICLA Nominations, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - ICLA Business June, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bonner Tagung der DGAVL, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - ICLA Council + Conference Brusells + Archival Research, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Paris May, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - CC New York, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 11th Editorial Conference, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 10th Editorial Conference, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 9th Editorial Conference, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 8th Editorial Conference, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 7th Editorial Conference, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 6th Editorial Conference, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 5th Editorial Conference, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 4th Editorial Conference, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 3rd Editorial Conference, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 2nd Editorial Conference, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 1st Editorial Conference, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Interim Report January, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - RPF Outline January, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Corres. re. Interim References January, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Report to CC Pretoria 2000 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - CC La divina commedia, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Early Outlines of RFP, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Prose Poem/Verse Romance, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - RNFP (Corrections), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Romantic Drama, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Congress Workshop, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Report on Romantic Poetry (CC), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Workshop #8 (Maternite), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Preforia Workshop #8 (Modernity), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Romantic Prose Project, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Division Roman + 19th century, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Roman Fiction/Prose (ICLA), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Romantic Prose, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Reports to CC on Rom. + Memos on Rom volumes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Romantic Prose Fiction + Editorial Team Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Division Comparative Studies in Rom. + 19th Century, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Reviews of RPF, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - RPF, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - LR/RL, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Edinburgh A.A. Parker, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 104 German HIstory of Literature, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - China Committee '88 ff, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Comparative Concepts of Self, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ACLA + CL., 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - ACLA + SCLA, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Australia + New Zealand, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Argentina, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Jordanas Andinas, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Austria, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Société Belge de Litt. G+C & Société Luxembourg, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Estonia, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - FILLM, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Brazil, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - New Comparison, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - The Comparatist, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Canada, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - China (1996ff) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - East Anglia Spring 1987-88, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - UEA Absurdist Drama, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - UEA Literature of Decadence, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Far Eastern/East-West Scholars, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - IVG, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Greece, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Hungary 1994ff, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - India, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Sahitya Akademi Film + Narrative, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Israel (Poetics Today), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Italy, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Japan, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Mexico, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Netherlands, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Near East (including Egypt), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Norway (Bergen/Saetre), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Poland, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Portugal, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Ass. Portugesa de Lit Comp., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Romania, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Serbia, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Singapore, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Saval, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sociedad Espanola, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - SELGyC, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Switzerland (ICLA), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Taiwan (Claroc) Hong Kong, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Vietnam, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Rebuilding ICLA, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - XIVth Congress of the Intl. Comparitive Lit. Association, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - ICLA Nominations, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Dakar Meeting of ICLA, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Pretoria 2nd Circular Ablage 1st Circular, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - DGAVL (Germany), 2000 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - France + SFLGC, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - BCLA, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - BCLA July 2-6, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - New Comparison, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Lieven Dh. May, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Taskforce on Committees, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Taskforce Draft B, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Taskforce Draft A, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Interim Report + Annexes, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Taskforce Draft C, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Taskforce Draft D + D1, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Taskforce Inequities, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Communications Strategy, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Committee on Publication Policy, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Commission on Research, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Central + South American Committee, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - East + South East European Committee, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Nominations + Materials Bulletin, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Research Committee Reports I-IV+, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Reports of Com. V-Vii + Reports of Adm. Coms. i + ii, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - G.G. Leiden duties/calendars, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Panels (Leiden), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Notes for Remarks to Gen. Ass., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Reports of Secs. + Treas., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Secretariat - Leiden Cong., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cornea - Comon Public + Res. Policy, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Congress 2000 (Leiden) EC (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Reports of Res. Com. (Leiden), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Reports on Congress Publications + Conference (Leiden), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Leiden Org./Selected Committees, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Nominations-->Leiden Congress, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Odense Agenda + Program Schedule, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Names (EC + Guests) Addresses, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - FILLM (1994ff) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Publication of Proceedings XIVth Congress, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - G.G. Rio Workshop Response, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - ICLA + ACLA Business + Colleagues Current, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CL/CLS/Comparitist Consultancy, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - NEA Consultancy, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Planning Committee --> D. Figueira, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Darko matter, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Lecture Tour Germany May, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Athens, Georgia ICLA meeting, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Athens, Georgia ICLA conference, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Athens schedule, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Ashland Shakespeare September, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Gastprofessur Hagen, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Seminar material Hagen, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Gastprofessur Hagen, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mainz Materials, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Indiana April 5-8, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Reading Version Inter Arts Indiana, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Dedalus ms. (Portugal), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - River Voyages, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Relevance of Irrelevance (corrected), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Visionary Peaks, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Ren-Bar., undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - UC Santa Barbara La Picara, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Browning Festschrift, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - The Fine Art of Erotic Dream, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Mysterious + Terrifying others, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Agents of History, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - 18th c. Dream (draft), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Imagined, Witnessed, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - PAMLA November, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Theater Three, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Houston February, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Assembly of the Gods, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Prometheus, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Hieroglyphics of Finality, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Festschrift for W. Veit, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Indiana Roman Conference September, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Oedipus #4, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 19th cen., 20th cen., (post)modernism, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Mult in High Mod., undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Mallarmé + Germany, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - The Living Palmipsest, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Donoso, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fantasy Studies, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Progression du Mythe, et la mythe du progres, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Progress of Myth Early Draft, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Barth, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Short-Story Cycle Materials, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Papers including John Barth, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - PAPC Forum PAMLA, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Insd. f. Humane Studies (George Mason), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Citizen Ambassador Program, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Seidlin Bio - + Bibliography, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Niemeyer - re Seidlin, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - English Speaking Union, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - ALSC Council, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Literary Imagination Advisory Board, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Prier, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Report, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 12th Congress ICLA (Historical File), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Stanford 12th Congress, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Culture Wars at Stanford, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Binghamton University, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Research Foundation, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - CTIC, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - P/CISMI, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Vita: A. Gillespie, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Adrienne's Educational Correspondence, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Teaching Courses & Other Lists, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Courses, 1990-1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Stanford - Class Lists & Students' Grades, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - SU Grades, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Class Observations, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Students' Comments, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Review of CL at Stanford, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Research Account, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Recommenders, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Student Letters, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Grant Application to SU (personal), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - CL Personalities & Currents, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Report, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Sabbatical Plans, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Summer, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - University, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - C.L., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Comparative Literature, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Comparative Literature, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Comparative Literature Speakers, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Modern Thought and Literature, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Comparative Literature, 1980-1985 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Comparative Literature, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - G.G. Courses, 1984-1994 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Courses, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Sabbatical/Retirement/Courses, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Faculty Report, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Faculty Report, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Summer, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - G.G. Calendar, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Faculty Report, 1994-1995,1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Report, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Report, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Report, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sabbatical, 1990-1991, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Report, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Report, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - University, 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Report, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Report, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Report, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Report, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Report, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Report, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Report, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Report, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sabbatical, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Report, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Report, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Report, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Sabbatical, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Report, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-122
  - AILC-ICLA XV materials, 1997 Aug 16-22 (Box 1)